## EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF ARTS | DOUBLE MAJOR

Digital Design & Internet Communications Curtin University | 2018 - 2020

### WA CERTIFICATE OF EDUCATION

Hale School | 2010 - 2015

# **SKILLS & EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, PHP
- CSS, Sass
- Wordpress CMS
- React
- Vue JS
- Search Engine Optimisation (SEO)

# UI/UX DESIGN

- Figma Prototyping
- Adobe XD Prototyping
- Audit Reporting
- Sitemapping
- User journey maps
- User personas
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

- Project leading and management
- Client facing and ability to connect
- Personable and engaging
- Passionate for exceeding client expectations

# THOMAS BRENNAN

WEB DEVELOPER & UI/UX DESIGNER

PORTFOLIO: TBRENNAN.IO

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm passionate, really passionate about building unique and satisfying online experiences; about exceeding client expectations, digging deep to understand their wants and desires. It gets me out of bed every day, fills my thoughts, drives me. I've only been in this industry for just under 24 months, but I'm hooked. I'm raw, I'm young but I've already learned so much. I love collaborating with my team, inspiring each other to find solutions and push boundaries. So that's me; passionate, collaborative, solutions focussed and ready for the next challenge.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

DECEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

## FRONT END DEVELOPER & UI/UX DESIGNER

SLICK DESIGN PTY LTD

- Interned at the Slick Design for two months following my graduation from Curtin University.
- After being offered a full time role, my ability to connect with clients was recognised and I was asked to lead client projects from design concept to development.
- My role spans from client-facing whereby I lead project meetings, to a more internal website design, development and general project management focus.
- Provide client support, quoting and general website updates, backend maintenance and improvements.
- Mentoring student interns with UI/UX design and front-end development feedback.

OCTOBER 2016 - MARCH 2020

#### **CURRENCY EXCHANGE CASHIER**

TRAVEL MONEY

- Responsible for providing high quality customer service to holiday-goers, issuing foreign currency cards and providing physical foreign currency cash conversions and sales.
- Maintaining both the company and parent company's tourism websites with current deals and general design improvements.

